<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
	<channel>
		<title>Consumed by saturdayxiii</title>
		<description>{&quot;meta&quot;=&gt;&quot;This is my personal consumption blog. Whether it be movies, shows, games, or actual food; if it has my attention I hope to feature it here.&quot;, &quot;subtitle&quot;=&gt;&quot;This is my personal consumption blog. Whether it be movies, shows, games, or actual food; if it has my attention I hope to feature it here.&quot;}</description>
		<link>http://localhost:4000</link>
		<atom:link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
		
			<item>
				<title>Truth and Reconciliation Day</title>
				
					
						<dc:creator>{&quot;name&quot;=&gt;&quot;saturdayxiii&quot;, &quot;email&quot;=&gt;nil, &quot;info&quot;=&gt;nil}</dc:creator>
					
				
				
					<description>&lt;p&gt;Tomorrow is Truth and Reconciliation Day.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I had a friend ask what that was, so I told him about the bodies from Residential Schools, and how that was just the tip of the iceberg.  He said “Wow, now that’s proof that the government is out to get us.  It’s really us vs them.”  Now, I can’t speak to priority of class issues in my friend’s background, but I can say that for white upper-middle class Canadians like me, we are the Them in “us vs them”.  We can point the blame at our government and churches, but they were still our government, and our churches.  Our inaction has caused just as much destruction as the actions that were delberately designed to destroy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now the narrative is often being shifted to how vaccines are the governments new weapon of choice.  And it’s true that medicine has been weaponized against visible minorities in the past, and still today, but as far as the covid vaccines go, our wealthy and privledged have been the first in line to get the vaccines and we’ve been caught giving expired vaccines to first nations people.  That’s not a narrative that victimizes my people.  It’s the same narrative of us taking from those that need it, then trying to cut off access before they can get it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I really want to do, and be part of something better.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				
				<pubDate>Wed, 29 Sep 2021 00:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
				<link>http://localhost:4000//2021/09/29/Truth-and-Reconciliation-Day/</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000//2021/09/29/Truth-and-Reconciliation-Day/</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Pain au chocolat de la ghetto</title>
				
					
						<dc:creator>{&quot;name&quot;=&gt;&quot;saturdayxiii&quot;, &quot;email&quot;=&gt;nil, &quot;info&quot;=&gt;nil}</dc:creator>
					
				
				
					<description>
</description>
				
				<pubDate>Fri, 24 Sep 2021 00:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
				<link>http://localhost:4000//2021/09/24/pain-au-chocolate/</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000//2021/09/24/pain-au-chocolate/</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Escitalopram pt II</title>
				
					
						<dc:creator>{&quot;name&quot;=&gt;&quot;saturdayxiii&quot;, &quot;email&quot;=&gt;nil, &quot;info&quot;=&gt;nil}</dc:creator>
					
				
				
					<description>&lt;p&gt;Okay.  It’s been long enough for me to feel confident about my depression medicine experience.  I’m so.  So.  Lucky.  I’m just over 2 months in and I feel great.  Like literally, if you asked me “how are you doing?” I could honestly say “I feel happy”.  That’s never been the case, as far as I know.  It’s been that way for at least 2 weeks now.  It’s been a bit of a journey, so here’s a break down.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;week 1: drowsy + insomia + poor apetite + can’t orgasm + salt and starch over power other tastes&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;week 2: drowsy + poor apetite + can’t orgasm&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;week 3: drowsy + lower sex drive&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;week 4: drowsy to the point that I suggest to my doctor that I can’t keep this up.  He says try another month…ok.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;week 5: I stop drinking diet sodas and start taking &lt;a href=&quot;https://seed.com/&quot;&gt;Seed probiotics&lt;/a&gt;  Two days later I feel amazing.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;week 6: No issues.  I have some trouble getting up in the morning, but I always seem to have enough energy in the day.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;week 7: Great.  I need to figure out if this is the Escitalopram, or the seed pills, so I stop taking the seed pills.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;week 8: Great, but i run out of escitalopram.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;week 8.6: I still feel great.  Not sleeping as deeply, but still lots of energy, maybe even better social performance than usual.  I get my pescription refil.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;week 9.2: Overly relaxed.  I’m stretching a lot and trying not to sleep in, but I still feel great.  I’m confident that my fasting from Seed pills and diet soda has done next to nothing compared to the escitalopram.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What a weird journey.  My last walk in got a different Doctor.  Even if I don’t pay attention to the name and voice over the phone, I can still tell because new doctors always ask if I’ve tried to kill myself lately.  He said the typical protocol is to use the medication for 6 months, if effects have been positive, then stop…  Sounds odd.  I’m liking that I lasted 4 days without it, so maybe my chronic mental illness has a chance of correcting itself, long term, after 6 months of seratonin support?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Whatever, it’s so amazing to feel like I always thought I should be able to feel like.  I’ll take what I can get for now.  And I realize how super privledged I am to have things work out so easily.  I don’t know what I would have done if I had to keep digging to find the right medication.  Maybe one more time, maybe two more times, to what?  Develop a habbit?  I mean, it took me 11 years since my last therapist visit to actually get proper medication.  It’s a hard sell, if you don’t know.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It sucks, but if you’re in that position, please keep fighting.  I at least know that things that have always felt wrong do have the possibility of feeling right, so keep trying please.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				
				<pubDate>Fri, 17 Sep 2021 00:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
				<link>http://localhost:4000//2021/09/17/Escitalopram-II/</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000//2021/09/17/Escitalopram-II/</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Cucumber Soda</title>
				
					
						<dc:creator>{&quot;name&quot;=&gt;&quot;saturdayxiii&quot;, &quot;email&quot;=&gt;nil, &quot;info&quot;=&gt;nil}</dc:creator>
					
				
				
					<description>&lt;p&gt;Cucumber soda looks more fun than it tastes.  Makes me feel like a begrudged adult.  Lemon helps.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				
				<pubDate>Fri, 10 Sep 2021 00:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
				<link>http://localhost:4000//2021/09/10/Cucumber-Soda/</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000//2021/09/10/Cucumber-Soda/</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Brand New Cherry Flavor</title>
				
					
						<dc:creator>{&quot;name&quot;=&gt;&quot;saturdayxiii&quot;, &quot;email&quot;=&gt;nil, &quot;info&quot;=&gt;nil}</dc:creator>
					
				
				
					<description>&lt;p&gt;Yep.  Brand New Cherry Flavor was great.  Fantastic edition to the &lt;a href=&quot;https://saturdayxiii.github.io/2021/08/02/Channel-Zero-Dream-Door/&quot;&gt;Channel Zero&lt;/a&gt; series.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’ve seen criticisms of the ending, which aren’t wrong, but also kind of a given because Netflix needs to sequel bait.  However, I personally didn’t find it very disatisfying, I can handle dropping a show at a clif hanger though.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				
				<pubDate>Wed, 08 Sep 2021 00:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
				<link>http://localhost:4000//2021/09/08/Brand-New-Cherry-Flavor/</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000//2021/09/08/Brand-New-Cherry-Flavor/</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>3D Pixel Art</title>
				
					
						<dc:creator>{&quot;name&quot;=&gt;&quot;saturdayxiii&quot;, &quot;email&quot;=&gt;nil, &quot;info&quot;=&gt;nil}</dc:creator>
					
				
				
					<description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://bonecollectors.itch.io/dino-hazard&quot;&gt;Dino Hazard&lt;/a&gt; was my inspiration for revisiting Blender pixel art.  I love that SNES Jurassic Park asthetic, but that swf Game Maker pixel art has always triggered me.  I don’t think this matches the style as much as I was hoping, but it was a fun project.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				
				<pubDate>Tue, 31 Aug 2021 00:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
				<link>http://localhost:4000//2021/08/31/3D-Pixel-Art/</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000//2021/08/31/3D-Pixel-Art/</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Iontophoresis Part 2</title>
				
					
						<dc:creator>{&quot;name&quot;=&gt;&quot;saturdayxiii&quot;, &quot;email&quot;=&gt;nil, &quot;info&quot;=&gt;nil}</dc:creator>
					
				
				
					<description>&lt;p&gt;Long over due for an update on my &lt;a href=&quot;https://saturdayxiii.github.io/2021/05/19/iontophoresis/&quot;&gt;iontophoresis experiment&lt;/a&gt;… it worked!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As pictured, I’ve “upgraded” to a full body treatment.  I don’t think that is specificly working, at least not for everything.  Localized treatment definitely works best.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It took about 3 weeks to see improvements.  My feet aren’t dry-blistered from being soaked all day, so I’m sweating less, and my shoes smell, like, normal bad, rather than old cheeto bad.  My girlfriend has complained of my overall lack of scent, so I think the bath is working as well, but after a couple months of just that I noticed that I was having to swap my shoes more often again.  So since I’m already well established into the process, I do each: a full bath, and a foot-specific bath, once a week.  That seems to give me the best coverage.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I don’t think I have much specifics to add.  Other than, don’t accidently use AC.  That was exciting.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				
				<pubDate>Mon, 23 Aug 2021 00:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
				<link>http://localhost:4000//2021/08/23/iontophoresis-pt-2/</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000//2021/08/23/iontophoresis-pt-2/</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Blender Pixel Art</title>
				
					
						<dc:creator>{&quot;name&quot;=&gt;&quot;saturdayxiii&quot;, &quot;email&quot;=&gt;nil, &quot;info&quot;=&gt;nil}</dc:creator>
					
				
				
					<description>&lt;p&gt;I wanted to make some pixel art and having been introduced to Blender pixel art before, and loving how such a catch-all program Blender is, I decided that that’s what I wanted to do, but now I have to re-learn how to do that.  Well, it didn’t take long to find this video from &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCk0taWcQZnzVYN1qcSnwlpg&quot;&gt;Soyaa&lt;/a&gt; that is a fine tutorial, but more importantly has references in its description to learn every step in the process.  Wow.  I wish this wasn’t the last day of my weekend to go through this stuff.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;edit: As good as the tutorials are, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCEbQnZQQtzATJreYx78uw6A&quot;&gt;Mezaka’s&lt;/a&gt; plugin is &lt;a href=&quot;https://saturdayxiii.github.io/2021/08/31/3D-Pixel-Art/&quot;&gt;awesome&lt;/a&gt;.  Especially if you add the extra features he goes over in his video:
&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Cwh_TpouPfQ&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://i3.ytimg.com/vi/Cwh_TpouPfQ/maxresdefault.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;thumbnail&quot; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				
				<pubDate>Tue, 17 Aug 2021 00:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
				<link>http://localhost:4000//2021/08/17/Blender-Pixel-Art/</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000//2021/08/17/Blender-Pixel-Art/</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Chickpea Pasta</title>
				
					
						<dc:creator>{&quot;name&quot;=&gt;&quot;saturdayxiii&quot;, &quot;email&quot;=&gt;nil, &quot;info&quot;=&gt;nil}</dc:creator>
					
				
				
					<description>&lt;p&gt;Once again an ad on Facebook outed itself with a good idea that I could do much cheaper by myself.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Chickpea Pasta&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Made up the same as regular pasta: 3/4 cup of chickpea flower, an egg, and a dab of oil and salt.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It needs to be made much thinner than what I did though, as it really takes its time to cook through.  On the plus side it’s also very difficult to overcook, which is my main peeve with regular pasta.  It does have a noticeable chickpea taste, which is also a perk in my opinion.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Might be time to invest in a cheap pasta roller.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				
				<pubDate>Tue, 03 Aug 2021 00:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
				<link>http://localhost:4000//2021/08/03/chickpea-pasta/</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000//2021/08/03/chickpea-pasta/</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Channel Zero Dream Door</title>
				
					
						<dc:creator>{&quot;name&quot;=&gt;&quot;saturdayxiii&quot;, &quot;email&quot;=&gt;nil, &quot;info&quot;=&gt;nil}</dc:creator>
					
				
				
					<description>&lt;p&gt;I’m glad I never gave up on Channel Zero after that rough &lt;a href=&quot;https://saturdayxiii.github.io/2016/10/14/I-watched-the-first-episod/&quot;&gt;first season&lt;/a&gt;, though I probably should have said something about the other seasons as I watched them.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I enjoyed them.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This last one, which admittedly came out a while ago, was probably my favorite, though they’ve all had their high and low moments.  I loved Pretzel Jack, he’s adorable and &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.instagram.com/twistytroy&quot;&gt;Twisty Troy&lt;/a&gt; is amazing, and I remained amused even when the last episode devolved into synthy, contstruction area b-movie.
A great show.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And I do believe my intuition was kicking in for me to finally finish Channel Zero, as I’ve learned that Nick Antosca’s newest show, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.netflix.com/ca/title/80233374&quot;&gt;Brand New Cherry Flavor&lt;/a&gt;, is set to premier in a couple weeks.  Looking forward to that.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				
				<pubDate>Mon, 02 Aug 2021 00:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
				<link>http://localhost:4000//2021/08/02/Channel-Zero-Dream-Door/</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000//2021/08/02/Channel-Zero-Dream-Door/</guid>
			</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>
